(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-01T10:09:03.912928",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Oh, you... There is no one I adore more.
You, who must have risked life and limb to be here with me forevermore.
The last words I wrote before I was cast into this endless abyss by the immortals seeking to protect this world and all of its inhabitants...
wrapped in darkness, alone, void of all emotion.
I once more feel a presence, signaling my return. Love's fervent seal... a spark of light in this ocean.
Now, there is but little left for you to do before I am free and we can be together.
And those who trapped me within these pages shall rue locking away this beauty forever.
Only your love can set me free.
Go, recite the verse before you quickly... lest before me you bend and take a knee.
Once in a faraway, faraway world was a collar that cooed like a snake
I want someone, please, I need someone, please, oh, I listened close as it howled in ache
Please don't be angry and please don't abandon me, don't leave me here on my own
It wrapped itself tightly, daily and nightly, only with praise would it loosen its hold
I'm pleased in the cup of my clothes
There's no one left for me to surpass
Don't I look cute in this dress?
I really, really must confess, it's tightening round my neck
Give me your love, all of your love, give me your love, all you can conjure up
Give me your love, all of your love, till you go mad with ecstasy
All of the hurt, all of the ache, help me escape, take it, oh, take it away
Is there no end to this pain?
Grow as you may but the necklace will stay just as small as the day it was found
It's so suffocating the endless placating
No one is no one is ever enough
Won't lose to anyone always rank number one
Aren't I a beautiful child
I'm better than her I'm better than him
Oh everyone come 'round and gawk at perfection
meeting you right after school
and finally confessing to you
Ain't it too good to be true
A girl like me in love with you who's miserable vulgar and crude
Give me your love all of your love
give me your love you can have everything
If I have you I can have you
Shoulder my load now yours to behold
Still not enough you're not enough
never enough still I won't lose in my heart
Truly I'm so sorry give me your love all of your love
give me your love all you can conjure up
give me your love all of your love
'til you go mad with ecstasy
I know it hurts only gets worse
God how it hurts soon you'll be craving more pain
This is my happiness now
Did you enjoy my lovely song?
I hope you did.
It was for you, after all.
But...
why are you not smiling?
Are you not happy to see me?
Well?
Say something.
Answer me.
Who...
who are you?
What?
You don't know who I am?
But everyone knows.
You are the one that released me, right?
I'm...
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
For what?
For releasing me?
No, no, no. For upsetting you.
If I said something wrong, I apologize.
Apologize?
You, who should be amongst my most dearest and beloved followers,
who has freed me from that prison,
who has shown me your love above all others...
You then act like you don't even know who I am?
Why would you toy with my emotions?
I'm... I'm sorry, I'm not sure what you mean.
You're not sure what I mean?
Are you mocking me now?
If you truly do not know who I am,
then why is it that you set me free?
If not from my love and if not by your love, then for what?
Tell me the truth, and the whole truth, now.
No more lies, or there will be consequences.
I-I'm not lying.
I swear to you,
I have no idea how I released you.
I just came to a temple to collect rare spices and memories from the many books stowed away here.
By the gods, that's the whole truth!
Extract memories from books?
Are you telling me you're a witch?
How dare you step foot here!
Even knowing the long history between demons and witches, you still dare set foot here?
I know how witches dare to try and bind my kind.
Would you be foolish enough to dare attempt that on me?
Yes... Okay.
Yes, I'm a witch, but I've never... well, mostly never tried anything like that.
I-I swear!
And this time, I was not let on by my nature at all.
No, this time, it was an angel that spoke to me of this place.
An angel came to me in my dreams, and...
Told me of an enchanted book that centuries of memory stood away here.
Can you imagine the knowledge and stories hidden in centuries of memories?
With a prize like that, I had to come find a book, no matter the danger.
Little could I have known the true nature of the book, though.
Enough! I've heard enough.
I believe you are who you say you are: a witch.
But I don't fully believe your childish story. No angel would ever lead a witch to such a dangerous book.
And I can hardly believe it is just the book and not myself you are after.
It... It's true. An angel came to me in my dreams...
and told me to come here. I was drawn to that book,
with all its power and stories. And well, I guess, you inside it.
The powerful aura it gave off drew me right to it.
How was I to know that the aura was thanks to a demon trapped within its pages?
Though, now that I recount my story, it does seem it really was me who released you.
Speaking of coming and going, now that you are free, I think it is time I take my leave of this place.
I'm glad I was able to help free you from... from once again.
I didn't say you could leave.
You may leave when I say you can leave, and stop your nervous fidgeting.
I know, fool. You think I didn't see you reaching for your book of magic?
You, a witch, should know better than anyone that no amount of magic is powerful enough to destroy a demon of my power.
However, you can take some solace in the fact that if I had wanted you dead, you'd already be so.
The only reason you're still alive is because you helped free me.
Alas, I cannot allow a witch who so obviously came with the intent to bind me to her will leave here freely.
Your story did little to convince me your aims were otherwise.
So, I will give you an ultimatum: you serve me here in my hollow temple,
love me, adore me, worship me.
Every living day, give me all the love you have.
Or I can take your soul right now. Your choice.
Kiarah... I need you.
Lost in the rain with no umbrella
Nights nest out your eyes
Can't seem to find your way back home
Come in and be my guest
Such a lovely smile spread across your face, but it's simply forgery
If you need to hide from the world outside, why not try to be my guest
Waiting all day long, but your friends don't come and you're left there all alone
Still you can't jump off from the high rooftop, so come on and be my guest
Like a cat the way I step and step and step
Be careful as my feet go tap and tap and tap
We'll follow nicely with a snap and snap and snap
So lovely you'll be mesmerized by me
My institution's peaceful as can be, despite the way that it seems, both our quotes and our supports will be concise, clearly, clean
Since we're only starting out, there's some improbabilities
But just listen up tonight, you'll have to stay up peacefully
Friends? They don't like you
When you know it's true, still you're right there back and call
Since you're desperately given easily, come inside and be my guest
You're the last to choose, but your luck's confused
Seems that someone took your share
If you won't accuse 'cause you don't have proof, take your chance then be my guest
On the way back home, there's a sweet aroma
That tempts you off your path
I can't help but laugh 'cause I know in fact
Soon you're bound to be my guest.
Yo!
Demon! How dare you kill an innocent?
Excuse me! I've done no such thing.
Innocent?
I would hardly call a witch who lives for power and binds my kind for her own purposes innocent.
Very ideas laughable.
Leave, I have no quarrel with you, so go now in peace before I change my mind.
A small token for your past bravery and trials.
How gracious, don't think I can't see straight through your ploy still.
You will not escape justice, not this time.
You have brought this fight on yourself for your actions, demon.
We have brought all of this on yourself.
For what?
For killing a mere witch?
She was not just a witch, she was my friend and a kindhearted person.
And you killed her in cold blood.
Oh, the legendary Phoenix, the mighty fiery Kiara, friends with a witch?
It's almost funny, did you not realize?
It was your witch friend who freed me.
Liar!
She would never do such a ghastly thing.
I trust she would stay away from the dark magics and demonic rituals.
To suggest otherwise is just another one of your dark lies.
She didn't deserve to die.
Poor Phoenix, still so trusting of those around you and unable to see through their deceptions.
Your kind spirit constantly deceives you.
That witch was never your friend.
We all know they cannot be trusted, even after all these years you still have not changed, still believing in lies and still so easily misled.
Still such a fool.
It is you who is the fool, demon!
Your lust for love and attention continues to lead you down the path of death and destruction.
And you don't even see that you're the one destroying your own happiness.
The gods are right to confine you there, you who are still shackled by your lust for love,
your desire for attention, your desire to be worshipped.
I am the demon of sound!
How dare you speak to me in such a manner!
It is but right that all should worship me on their knees, their love for none but myself.
Leave! I have heard enough of your falsities, this is your last warning. Go now, or you'll be left to rot here forever.
I am not afraid of you, and I will heed no such warning.
Listen, and listen well, demon,
I will not allow you to claim any more victims.
To be banished in the void was not sufficient enough punishment for you.
No.
Now I will finish what the gods should have.
とべ、起こせ！ 願う は 事故
Fly, get moving! All I want is trouble.
一世 一代 さあ 何 賭す？ 自問 自答
Once in a lifetime, what do you bet on? Self-analysis!
勝つ か 負ける か ドロー なんて ない わ
It's about win or lose, there can't be a draw.
ah, ah, ah, hey 幕開ける わ
Ah, ah, ah, hey, let's open the curtains!
カッチング して ラッキー マネー どっち も むりー cigar, cigar
Catch it, lucky money, seems impossible... (Cigar, cigar!)
引ける か 否 か 自分 次第 だ な
You gonna pull out or no? It all depends on me, huh?
余裕 で！ 振り切り 全 bet だぜ い イェイ イェイ イェイ イェイ ☆！
Piece of cake! I'll bet it all and give it all I got! Yay, yay, yay, yay, ☆!
そこ どけ ！ そう この エース かっ さらう の は アタシ だ
Out of my way! Yeah, I'll be the one to snatch this ace.
stay もういい 勝た た なら 平常心
Stay, I've had enough! If I win, my mind will be at ease.
ね プレイボーイ 行け don't get in my way じゃあね 黙っ て
Hey, playboy, go ahead, don't get in my way, see ya, just shut up.
ワンツー スリー ワンツー スリー ワンツー スリー sit down, sit down
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three. Sit down, sit down.
はーもう フリーズ キメ て や
Ah, I'm already frozen, decide what to do.
投げる の は 骰 ！？ 才 ！？ か 匙 か ！？
Are you throwing the dice? Your talent? Or giving up?
そんな 小さい 尺度 じゃ はかれない でしょ そうでしょ セイ ・ グッド ・ バイ ァ
Such a small scale won't measure it. Right? That's right! Say goodbye!
あっち こっち そっち どっち ！？ nothing, nothing 病む
Here, there, everywhere, which way? Nothing, nothing, feeling sick.
道 なき 道 より 闇 々 悪
Darkness is way worse than a pathless path.
空回り し そう でも まだ 止め ない で
Even if it feels like spinning your wheels, don't stop yet.
あー の まれ そう 声 々 それぞれ に
Ah, about to be swallowed up by voices, each and every one.
get one's way ! アンタ は ここ まで
Get one's way! You've reached your limit.
後ろ だけ 見 とけ
Just keep your eyes on what's behind you.
one, two, three
I got skills as cold as ice
you gotta throw your hands up you can't decide
you gotta throw your hands up if you can't decide,
gonna scare you off as i roll the dice
p-ssies gotta say goodbye ya
had enough? you make a bluff, oh nothing, nothing has
Had enough? You make a bluff, oh, nothing, nothing, nothingness!
need to lie cause we can light it up, it up, it up
I’m spinning round, can’t avoid the voices in my head
I'm spinning round, can't avoid the voices in my head,
no stopping now, i just gotta win this game instead
get one’s way
Get one's way!
you bet I’m here to stay
You bet I'm here to stay,
and now it’s time to lean your place
and now it's time to learn your place!
streak is running, lucky money
smoking like a cigar cigar
acting funny, answer if I’m quitting, if I’m not
Acting funny, answer if I'm quitting, if I'm not.
make your bets, black or red, chips to spend
Make your bets, black or red, chips to spend, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
raise the stakes, play that ace, risk your life on a single game
stay with me
our luck will change, you'll see
not here to play? don’t get in my way, I’m always counting
Not here to play? Don't get in my way, I'm always counting!
one, two, three
sit down, sit down
way to say good bye, bye
way to say goodbye, bye.
one, two, three
sit down, sit down
I'm so sorry, Iris.
It has been so long.
Nerissa...
I'm so, so sorry this happened to you. It was not my intention.
What do you mean?
What was not your intention?
This... you being... then... the witch and...
Kiara too.
What?
Are you saying you sent the Phoenix here to slay me?
No, I didn't!
Well, yes, but it was not my intention!
Iris, what are you trying to tell me?
That you tried to kill me?
You were supposed to be my friend! We've been friends since the beginning!
Yes, of... yes! You sent Kiara to kill me?
No! No!
Then what?
Be clear. How is this how you greet your beloved friend after so long?
No, I... I would never send someone to kill you.
But yes, I'm still your loyal friend. I always have been, and always will be.
I... I tried to free you, and I did. I sent the witch. You're here to free you, and she did.
"I... I tried to free you, and I did. I sent the witch here to free you, and she did."
But I didn't know she was friends with Kiara, and when someone here threatened... I thought she would come alone.
This was not supposed to happen.
It was not my intention.
You sent... a witch to free me? Why would you send one who binds my kind for power?
Of all those in the world, a witch?
Why not send one of my most beloved followers? Only they are said to be able to free me.
Explain yourself.
What's going on?
I'm... I'm sorry. I have a lot to explain,
but we don't have time now.
We need to go. Now.
Death is coming for you.
What?
Please, come with me.
I know a way in which we can hide from death.
But we have to leave now before it's too late.
I'm not going anywhere with you until you explain to me what is going on.
Now! Why would you send a witch to free me, Iris?
Celia, I had no choice.
You had no choice.
You could have sent one of my followers instead.
You don't have any more followers! They're all dead!
They all died long ago.
What?
No, that... that can't be.
Has it been that long?
It's been over a thousand years since you've been locked away.
and your followers, they're all gone now.
It's been many long years since your name was whispered in these lands.
You mean... they... no longer... love me?
I... I'm sorry. I tried to free you as fast as I could.
I really did.
But it took a long time to work out how to free you and
"But it took a long time to work out how to free you,"
there was so much going on,
"and there was so much going on."
and the gods weren't about to look kindly on any trying to undo their work either.
"And the gods weren't about to look kindly on anyone trying to undo their work either."
I'm sorry. I don't have time to explain everything right now.
I understand. But, Iris...
Tell me...
Do you still love me?
What?
Yes, of course.
Then why do you lie to me?
I... I'm not lying, Nerissa!
Enough!
You of all people should understand
that a witch wouldn't be able to resist the power in my book and attempt to bind me.
And you can hardly expect me to believe that you, one of both planes, didn't know of the witch's connection to such a famed warrior.
This wasn't an attempt to free me... This...
this was an attempt to kill me!
To be free of me, to do what the gods couldn't! Get back!
Nerissa, that's not true! You don't understand!
Please give me some time to explain. But...
but not here! Death is coming for you, we have to go!
I'm not going anywhere with you!
Nerissa, surely by now Kiara's soul has arrived before Death! And what if Death finds out that you're free again?
We don't have much time! We have to go, now!
Please, Nerissa!
No... I don't believe you.
You've broken my spirit. To learn that my followers no longer love me was one thing...
...but to discover that my closest and most loyal friend has betrayed me... tried to kill me...
...and no longer loves me too.
If you no longer wish to give me your love, then I will take it.
遠ざかりはじめた その背中はもう振り戻れない
The back that began to fade away can no longer look back
長い夜が明けても
Even if the long night breaks,
過ちと罪は 今もずっと消えずに
the mistakes and sins still do not disappear
落ちる夕陽 闇が忍び寄り 黒く染まっていく純粋
The setting sun, darkness creeps closer, dyeing the purity black
想うほどに どうして傷で試した？
The more I think about it, why did I test you with wounds?
欲しかったのは唯一つ その笑顔なのに
All I wanted was that one smile
何度間違い続けた日々を 解いて結び直すように
As if untying and re-tying the days I kept making mistakes in
迷っても会いに行くよ 悲しい涙は拭いて
Even if I get lost, I will go to see you, wiping away your sad tears
いつの間にか忘れていた その優しい声を探して
Searching for that gentle voice I had forgotten before I knew it
また手を取り合えたなら 君ともう一度約束を交わそう
If we can hold hands once again, let's make a promise with you once more
途切れそうな可能性 見失わないように追いかけて
Chasing the fading possibility so as not to lose sight of it
手に入れたものなら 理想とは違う どこか欠けた愛情
As for what I got, it's love different from ideal, lacking somewhere
怒り嘆き 歪んだまま ぶつけ合う逆さまの言葉
Anger, grief, distorted, hitting each other with upside-down words
想うほどに どうして許せなかった？
The more I think about it, why couldn't I forgive?
守りたかった笑顔を 気づけば壊して
The smile I wanted to protect, before I knew it, I broke it
たとえすれ違い 離れていても 君を信じられたなら
Even if we pass each other and are apart, if I could believe in you
また逢える日が来たから 二人懐かしい顔で
Since the day we can meet again has come, with nostalgic faces for both of us
何気なく過ごしていた あの時を思い返すような
Like recalling that time we spent so casually
ありのまま通じ合えていた まるで運命のように
Able to communicate just as we are, as if it were destiny
失くしたものが もう戻らないこと わかっていても 願いをかけること 止められはしない
Even knowing that what has been lost will never return, I cannot stop making a wish
「いつか…」どれほど大切だった人だったのか 胸が苦しむ度に知った
"Someday..." I learned every time my chest ached how precious a person you were
ともに過ごした日を 笑い合った日々にを
The days we spent together, the days we laughed together
何度間違い続けた日々を 解いて結び直すように
As if untying and re-tying the days I kept making mistakes in
迷っても会いに行くよ 悲しい涙は拭いて
Even if I get lost, I will go to see you, wiping away your sad tears
いつの間にか忘れていた その優しい声を探して
Searching for that gentle voice I had forgotten before I knew it
また手を取り合えたなら 君ともう一度約束を交わそう きっと…
If we can hold hands once again, let's make a promise with you once more, surely...
なくしたものが もう戻らないこと
That what has been lost will never return
わかっていても 願いをかけること 止められはしない
Even knowing it, I cannot stop making a wish
「いつか…」どれほど大切だった人だったのか 胸が苦しむ度に知った
"Someday..." I learned every time my chest ached how precious you were
ともに過ごした日を 笑い合った日々に…
The days we spent together, the days we laughed together...
笑い合った日々を
The days when we laughed together
何度間違い続けた日々を
The days of endless mistakes
迷っても会いに行くよ
Even if I get lost, I'll go meet you
Kiara... Dead?
Never thought I'd see the day.
But tell me, what laid you low?
I must know, is there a foe that could bring this about,
and even fewer who would give you reason to voyage on through my blackened halls and not return to the world of the living as a hatchling?
Must be urgent, whatever it is.
Forgive me, but I felt this was something you needed to hear urgently.
I was slain by one with whom you are quite familiar,
a tyrant of darkness, one out to bring all the world under her domain, to worship her for all eternity.
It can't be.
I'm afraid the demon of sound has been freed from the void again and is in the world once more; her long confinement has ended,
and she is the same as she has ever been, quick to anger, blinded by her lust for adoration.
And this time, I was the second victim of her lust for love and blood.
You? Murdered by that love-obsessed demon?
Yes. And her first victim was a good friend of mine, too.
Forgive me, Lord Death, but this injustice cannot stand;
unfortunately, her power is already beyond my ability to stop.
Please, you must do something to stop that monster;
she will surely only take more lives and plunge the world into further chaos.
Come on, quick, ascend to the world of the living with your great scythe in hand
and reap the life of the demon of sound before she can claim another victim.
Avenge my life and the life of my friend, I beg you.
That demon cannot be left to ravage the world once more; I warned the other gods before, but here we are;
it is time I take this into my own hand and do what I should have done long ago.
Your demonic side was always to be the death of you, IRyS.
Don't you dare speak her name.
Silence.
Your bloodlust and desire for adoration has clouded your judgment
to the point where you can't even tell friend from foe anymore.
You're the one who brought bloody doom upon your own beloved friend, and yourself;
your fear of losing your hold over things brings about the very result you so fear.
How dare you continue on with your excuses,
blame who you will for your own misdoing if you wish;
in the end, you have only yourself to blame
for the situation you find yourself in.
A lust for love so strong that those you love turn away,
a desire for power so overwhelming, those you have power over turn on you.
In anger so deep that you destroy all who might have helped save you,
your fate has been sealed by your own hand.
And now, I am now here to deliver it to you.
Why do you get to decide who lives or dies?
You who sits alone in your own realm, Empress of all,
both life and death at your fingertips.
could you possibly know about the desire
for the love and adoration of others,
you who already has everything?
You, and all the gods, all full of yourselves and so ready to look down upon those of us who fight for more...
mouths full of twisted tongues...
Their hearts rot with jealousy.
They're jealous of me! Spiteful that I was loved more!
Again, you cannot see past your own desires.
The gods took pity on you and your kind.
When I created you, the first demon, the gods felt it unjust and dangerous for such a being to exist for the sole purpose of watching over the surface in my stead...
to be mindless...
soulless.
So, they gave the demon a psyche, and plucked it from my deepest and blackest halls,
freering it to roam amongst the two worlds whenever it pleased.
freeing it to roam amongst the two worlds whenever it pleased.
I warned them that the demonic nature was too strong and dangerous to give such desires,
and far too dangerous for such a being to exist alongside the mortals.
But the others persisted, and now, here we are, my unheeded warnings leading us back to where it all started.
You almost plunged the world into chaos due to your unbridled lust for adoration.
Time and time again, you gave in to your nature, banishing you to a void which was supposed to be a chance for you to reflect on your past, but has only proven that you are truly unfit for this world.
アイアイアイヘイトユー な な な な なん ですの
I-i-i hate you! W-w-w-what about it?
君がなきゃあたしは無い 無い
Without you living here, I'd probably just disappear!
はい はい そうですね その通りです
Right, right! Right you are!
喉を過ぎる解の有様
What, wanna round of applause?
あ あ あ
Ah, ah, ah...
アイアイアイヘイトユー な な な な なん ですの
I-i-i hate you! W-w-w-what about it?
君は軽薄 くたびれ だらけ
The way you're flippant and your limbs are filled with fatigue
あたしいい子じゃいられない
A 'good girl' life just ain't for me,
それは常にしりしり
In fact, closer to that would be...
あなたワイワイワイドンチュノウ てんでだめですの
Why, why, why don't you know? A question of questionable help
意味があるなら言葉にせずに ただ態度で示さなきゃ
If you really mean it, show it with your attitude and tone
全てが伝わらないままに トップシークレット 明かさないように
Leaving everything unsaid, top secret, keeping it under wraps
そう
That's right.
アイアイアイヘイトユー な な な な なん ですの
I-i-i hate you! W-w-w-what about it?
君がなきゃあたしは無い 無い
Without you living here, I'd probably just disappear!
はい はい そうですね その通りです
Right, right! Right you are!
喉を過ぎればそれは真実
If you believe it, the word of mouth is surely truth
あ あ あ あ あるべき場所へ
To the place where it belongs
あ あ あ あ あたし導く
Dragging me along
あ あ あ あ 奈落の底で
To an abyss' edge
アイアイアイヘイトユー なん ですのかさり
I-i-i hate you! What about it's wrong? Festering
アイアイアイヘイトユー な な な な なん ですの
I-i-i hate you! W-w-w-what about it?
君が居るからあたしが痛い 痛い ハイハイそうですねその通りです極を超えては落ちてくの
The fact that you exist persists to bring me so much pain...
アイアイアイヘイトユー な な な な なん ですの
I-i-i hate you! W-w-w-what about it?
あたし期待 期待 無い連中 な な な な なん ですの
Without you living here, I'd probably just disappear...
どうにもならぬ
With no time to even think...
アイアイアイヘイトユー な な な な なん ですの
I-i-i hate you! W-w-w-what about it?
君がいまかいまかと高値盗の
Without you living here, I'd probably just disappear!
シークレット 愛に二日酔い初動が喉を焼けどさざる
Secret, secret...
シークレット シークレットに間に合え
Secret, secret in time!
アイアイアイヘイトユー な な な な なん ですの
I-i-i hate you! W-w-w-what about it?
君が居るからあたしが痛い痛い ハイハイそうですねその通りです
The fact that you exist persists to bring me so much pain...
欲を越えてはほしくたくの
...
アイアイアイヘイトユー な な な な なん ですの
I-i-i hate you! W-w-w-what about it?
あたしいたいいたいない
I'm in so much pain!
ハイアイアイソデスネソノトオリデスノー
Right, right! Right you are!
アイアイアイヘイトユー な な な な なん ですの
I-i-i hate you! W-w-w-what about it?
君がなきゃあたしは無い 無い
Without you living here, I'd probably just disappear!
はい はい そうですね その通りです
Right, right! Right you are!
喉を過ぎる解の有様
What, wanna round of applause?
ああ ああ ああ...
Ah, ah, ah...
Oh, such a misguided fool.
Your reckless ways have brought black doom upon yourself and those most beloved around you.
Blaming your misery on others when your demise was in fact forged by your own hands.
While you have earned your death in full, it is with pity,
not anger, that this blade falls upon you.
街明かり華やか
The bustling city and its neon lights,
エーテル麻痺の冷たさ
a touch of ether that's cold as ice,
眠れない午前二時 全てが急速に変わる
It's 2 AM and I can hardly sleep 'cause everything keeps changing rapidly,
オイル切れのライター
I'm like a lighter that's all out of gas,
焼け付くような胃の中
My insides are on fire,
全てがそう嘘なら 本当によかったのにね
If only everything was a lie, things would be so much better,
君の首を締め付ける夢を見た
I had a dream where these hands of mine were strangling your neck,
光の溢れる昼下がり
On a bright, sunny afternoon,
君の細い喉が跳ねるのを
I watched your slender throat twitch,
泣き出しそうな眼で見ていた
As my eyes welled up with tears,
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたいと思う
I want to throw myself into a nuclear reactor,
真っ青な光包まれて綺麗
And its pale blue light would envelop me so beautifully,
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたら そしたら すべてが許されるような気がして
If I could throw myself into a nuclear reactor, then everything might be okay, I might be forgiven,
ベランダの向こう側 階段を昇っていく音
On the other side of the veranda, I hear footsteps ascending the stairs,
陰り出した空が 窓ガラスに 部屋に落ちる
As the clouds creep over the sunlight, it drips through my window and into my room,
拡散する夕暮れ 泣き腫らしようような日の赤
Twilight scatters across the horizon, red like eyes swollen by tears,
溶けるように少しずつ 少しずつ 死んでいく世界
Slowly but steadily, the world is dying,
君の首を締める夢を見た
I had a dream where these hands of mine were strangling your neck,
春風に揺れるカーテン
My curtains were swaying gently in the spring breeze,
乾いて切れた唇から 零れる言葉は泡のよう
Your dry, parched lips mustered up, words that would vanish like foam on the waves,
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたいと思う
I want to throw myself into a nuclear reactor,
真っ白に 記憶 溶かされて消える
Into the shining, white light my memories will fade and disappear,
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたら また昔みたいに 眠れるような そんな気がして
If I could throw myself into a nuclear reactor, I might be able to sleep like I used to and everything might be okay,
時計の秒針や テレビの司会者や そこにいるけど見えない誰かの
The second hand on the clock, and the host on the television,
笑い声は和して反射する アレグロ・アジテート 耳鳴りがきけないやまない
There's someone there, but I just can't see them, their laughter swells and grows into an endless echo,
アレグロ・アジテート 耳鳴りがきけないやまない
Allegro agitate, the ringing in my ears won't stop, it won't go away,
Allegro agitato
耳鳴りが 消えない 止まらない
The ringing in my ears won't stop, it won't go away
Allegro agitato
耳鳴りが 消えない 止まらない
The ringing in my ears won't stop, it won't go away
誰もみみみな 消えてく 夢を見た
I had a dream where the whole entire world disappeared
真夜中の 部屋の広さと静寂が
Tonight, I'm swallowed by the vastness of my dark room
胸に突っかかって
Yet, silence closes in and suffocates me
上手に 息ができなくなり
My lungs can't find the air I need to breath
核融合炉にさ 飛び込んでみたら そうしたら
If I could throw myself into a nuclear reactor
きっと 眠るように 消えていけるんだ
Then I could finally fade away, as easily as closing my eyes to sleep
僕のいない 朝は 今より ずっと素晴らしくて
A new dawn without me would surely be dazzling new day
全ての 歯車が噛み合った
All of the gears would be turning together in harmony
きっと そんな 世界だ
Surely, that's how the world would be
Hi, darlings, and welcome to my 3D concert.
My first technically solo one.
As you can see up here is the hashtag for today, which is #RequiemforLove3D.
I'm watching the chat.
Did you guys enjoy it?
Did you like it?
Did you have fun? I should hope so.
Well, obviously a lot just happened,
but I must let you all know this was all a musical,
so none of it was real.
No one is no one is hurt.
There was no hololive girls hurt in the making of this musical,
so please don't worry.
This stage is awesome,
so I want to give it up to the team over at hololive Productions who put this all together.
Can we just take a look, take a moment to admire this beautiful stage before us?
Some of the more lesser shown details I kind of wanted to highlight a little bit.
So, let's go ahead and take a look at maybe the moon, maybe.
Look at that big thing in the background. It was also dark red at one point,
but currently it is, as it probably should be, normal, beautiful, because I was killed.
So we also have the giant castle in the background,
which is, oh my gosh, I was so excited for this. I was like, oh, I want something that's really kind of like cathedralsque and dark and gothic, and they fully delivered.
I'm so, so pleased with how it ended up looking in the final.
So, so happy.
We also have the beautiful stained glass if you can take a look.
It's a back there, these ones were actually screens, but we also have the ones on the side that were a little bit broken, but could also change as well.
So, very very fun.
It was kind of something that I was like, oh, I wonder how it's going to go, but I think it ended up looking really cool, right?
Lastly, we have all of these lovely flowers out in front.
Um, lastly, we have all of these lovely flowers out in front.
I just thought they came out so pretty, and I like how they kind of change throughout.
Uh, I just thought they came out so pretty, and I like how they kind of change throughout.
So it just kind of looked like nothingness, like a little void of like dead plants, but then at the end they all bloomed and it was so beautiful and I'm like, oh gosh.
I was so nervous.
And you might have noticed also something's a little different about me today.
Do you see anything different?
My wings are out.
I I decided since we've known each other for kind of a long time now that maybe it was finally time to uh stop pretending they're a coat and actually show you what they were.
But I did decide to take off my arm warmers a little bit just cuz, you04:44.200
But I did decide to take off my arm warmers a little bit just cuz, you know, I was feeling a little warm after all of that movement.
So, I'd love to show you the wings, so I'm going to open them up for you and to try flying for a little bit.
So,
What?
Yeah, there we go.
What do you think? I am capable
flight?
Obviously, it's a little
It's a little slow, but I'm working on it.
I'm working on my muscles. So,
I'll figure it out eventually.
I was locked up for like 9,000 years.
Cut me some slack.
Well, this is all very exciting.
So again, I'm so happy to have you here.
I wanted to talk a little bit about...
I have an announcement after this, but before that, I wanted to talk a little bit about...
just the making of this.
We had so many lovely guests first and foremost.
Well, we had so many lovely guests.
First and foremost...
First, we started off with Shiori Novella, who was our beautiful, cute witch who came here maybe not knowing what she was getting into.
Then, we had Takanashi Kiara, the brave, amazing Phoenix came in trying to avenge her friend, but ended up getting bested by the best.
Then, we had Iris, my Nephilim friend. Friends, as we're both demons, kind of.
And then, last but not least, of course, we had the Calliope Mori come in and take my life, as she should have. Because, wow, I was kind of... I was kind of mean in that musical. Don't you think?
Not not exactly the way that I usually am. So kind, but...
Regardless, it was really fun. I came up with the idea for the story and I wanted something that was like a little more exciting, a little more Tunibio.
'Cause deep down, I am cringe, but I am free.
So I hope you enjoyed the concept. We had amazing scriptwriters and just the whole team working on all of this was so amazing. So thank you for everyone who put in their efforts into this. It seriously means so much to me and audience, Jailbirds, thank you so much for watching. I hope you had a wonderful time.
And now, it is time for an important announcement.
This is my celebration merch, Nerissa Ravencroft 850k subscribers celebration.
So let's go ahead and take a look at the details, next up, or first up, I suppose.
"Your assignment has arrived" Plush Blanket, this is a plush blanket featuring an illustration by basically my second mama Yomosaka at this point, who also did the promotional art or the the like main cover art for this musical today.
Um, so it's very lovely. All of the merch today is going to be themed off of the DEO outfit. Again, so beautiful, so gorgeous. You can cuddle up with it at night if you're feeling lonesome, so highly recommend grabbing it.
Next up, we have the DEO Nerissa Voice Keychain. This illustration is by noka. This is a cute keychain, of course, you can carry it around with you everywhere. And in case you miss the sound of my voice, it has my voice in it about six different voice samples.
Next up is the Nerissa Ravencroft Hand Puppet. Um, I really wanted one and I thought you guys would too. And especially with the sexy DEO outfit, I just thought it made sense.
Next up is the last item, which is the "Match with Me!" Necklace. This features the necklace from my DEO outfit. It is silver and it has a tiny amethyst colored gem, because it's kind of hard to tell, but the gem on my actual necklace is not red. It is actually kind of purply.
Complete set purchase bonus, limited edition version. It's going to come with a postcard with a handwritten autograph by yours truly. And of course, the art is going to be the same one that's featured in the plush blanket, the art by Yomosaka-san.
Next up is the regular complete set. This is going to come with a postcard with a duplicated foil stamped autograph by me in the case that you miss out on the limited, but you'll still get my signature either way, so don't worry too much.
Both the limited and complete set are going to become with a bonus voice pack called "A Late Night at the Office" featuring me, of course, and you, who works in my office, jailbird.
So that is all of my merchandise. Please, please buy it. I hope you like it. Again, this is a celebration for 850k and I would be remiss to not say that this is all thanks to you guys and your support. So thank you so, so much for supporting me, for
Following me for watching my covers,
for watching this today, watching my streams,
commenting everything you guys do, I'm so grateful,
thank you so much. So that's the
final full set.
And and yeah, it's all good.
And yeah, it's all good.
So, please buy it.
I hope you guys like it.
I hope you're looking forward to receiving the items if you're buying it.
They will go live right after this, I believe.
So go ahead and check the description, it should have all the information right below.
So, thank you all so much, and that's that.
So, I guess I should say goodbye.
So, I don't want to, though I'm having so much fun today
dancing with everyone and singing for you guys...
But I'm so grateful I could spend time with you
and share this special moment with you.
I hope you guys all had a lot of fun,
and I'll look forward to seeing you all in my next stream.
So, for now, bye, darlings!
REQUIEM for LOVE
[Title: REQUIEM for LOVE]